import '../classes/quiz_class.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> narutoQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which Hokage sealed the nine-tailed fox inside Naruto?",
    answer1: "First Hokage",
    answer2: "Second Hokage",
    answer3: "Third Hokage",
    answer4: "Fourth Hokage",
    correctAnswer: "Fourth Hokage"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who tricked Naruto into stealing a sacred scroll?",
    answer1: "Zabuza",
    answer2: "Iruka",
    answer3: "Mizuki",
    answer4: "Sasuke",
    correctAnswer: "Mizuki"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which character can only use taijutsu?",
    answer1: "Uzumaki Naruto",
    answer2: "Rock Lee",
    answer3: "Uchiha Sasuke",
    answer4: "Gara",
    correctAnswer: "Rock Lee"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Naruto first shows his nine-tails chakra when he fights who?",
    answer1: " Neji Hyuuga",
    answer2: "Uchiha Sasuke",
    answer3: "Haku",
    answer4: "Gara",
    correctAnswer: "Haku"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",
    answer1: "Lotus of Destruction",
    answer2: "Shadow Lotus",
    answer3: "Primary Lotus",
    answer4: "Fiery Lotus",
    correctAnswer: "Primary Lotus"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Sasuke's goal is gain enough power to kill whom?",
    answer1: "The Third Hokage",
    answer2: "Uzumaki Naruto",
    answer3: "Uchiha Itatchi",
    answer4: "Hyuuga Neji",
    correctAnswer: "Uchiha Itatchi"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does 'Chidori' mean?",
    answer1: "One Thousand Birds",
    answer2: "Five Thousand Swords",
    answer3: "Five Hundred Punches",
    answer4: "Ten Thousand Stones",
    correctAnswer: "One Thousand Birds"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which of the legendary sannin becomes the fifth Hokage?",
    answer1: "Jiraya",
    answer2: "Tsunade",
    answer3: "Orochimaru",
    answer4: "Kakashi",
    correctAnswer: "Tsunade"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "D-rank missions are usually given to what level of shinobi?",
    answer1: "Chunin",
    answer2: "Genin",
    answer3: "Jonin",
    answer4: "Hokage",
    correctAnswer: "Genin"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Every member of Akatsuki is a what?",
    answer1: "S-rank criminal",
    answer2: "Kage",
    answer3: "Kunoichi",
    answer4: "Swordsman",
    correctAnswer: "S-rank criminal"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the relationship between Naruto and Iruka?",
    answer1: "Their parents were killed when they were younger",
    answer2: "Iruka was Naruto's teacher",
    answer3: "Were both class clowns in school",
    answer4: "All of these",
    correctAnswer: "All of these"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which of the following ninjas is a kunoichi?",
    answer1: "Orochimaru",
    answer2: "Uzumaki Naruto",
    answer3: "Haruno Sakura",
    answer4: "Gaara",
    correctAnswer: "Haruno Sakura"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "The Sharingan is what type of jutsu?",
    answer1: "Ninjutsu",
    answer2: "Doujutsu",
    answer3: "Genjutsu",
    answer4: "Taijutsu",
    correctAnswer: "Doujutsu"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the village where Naruto lives called?",
    answer1: "Kyuubigakure",
    answer2: "Konohagakure",
    answer3: "Sunagakure",
    answer4: "Uzamagakure",
    correctAnswer: "Konohagakure"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which of these is NOT a member of the Nara clan?",
    answer1: "Jiraiya",
    answer2: "Shikaku",
    answer3: "Ensui",
    answer4: "Yoshino",
    correctAnswer: "Jiraiya"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which of these people has been Hokage the most?",
    answer1: "Hashirama",
    answer2: "Sartuobi",
    answer3: "Tsunade",
    answer4: "Kakashi",
    correctAnswer: "Sartuobi"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who has not been considered for Hogake?",
    answer1: "Shikamaru",
    answer2: "Danzo",
    answer3: "Sakura",
    answer4: "Jiraya",
    correctAnswer: "Sakura"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which famed clan was completely massacred?",
    answer1: "Uchiha",
    answer2: "Nara",
    answer3: "Uzumaki",
    answer4: "Hyuuga",
    correctAnswer: "Uchiha"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which of these is NOT one of Naruto's specialties?",
    answer1: "Shadow Clone Jutsu",
    answer2: "Chidori",
    answer3: "Rasengun",
    answer4: "One Thouand Years Of Death",
    correctAnswer: "Chidori"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "How did Hidan die?",
    answer1: "He didn't die",
    answer2: "He Was Starved",
    answer3: "He was trapped in Shadow Posession Jutsu",
    answer4: "His own God betrayed him",
    correctAnswer: "He didn't die"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is Tsunade's \"drug\"?",
    answer1: "Men",
    answer2: "Alcohol",
    answer3: "Work",
    answer4: "Gambling",
    correctAnswer: "Gambling"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which friend died during the Fourth Great War?",
    answer1: "Neji",
    answer2: "Choji",
    answer3: "Hinata",
    answer4: "Shikamaru",
    correctAnswer: "Neji"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which ninja cannot do ninjutsu?",
    answer1: "Rock Lee",
    answer2: "Kakshi",
    answer3: "TenTen",
    answer4: "Neji",
    correctAnswer: "Rock Lee"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who does Naruto eventually marry?",
    answer1: "Temari",
    answer2: "Hinata",
    answer3: "Sajura",
    answer4: "TenTen",
    correctAnswer: "Hinata"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is Team Asuma's favorite food?",
    answer1: "Ramen",
    answer2: "Taiyaki",
    answer3: "BBQ",
    answer4: "Sushi",
    correctAnswer: "BBQ"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which trait is common in the Uzumaki clan?",
    answer1: "Abitilty to use rasengun",
    answer2: "Red hair",
    answer3: "Blue eyes",
    answer4: "Spunk",
    correctAnswer: "Red hair"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who gave their life to Gaara?",
    answer1: "Kankuro",
    answer2: "Sasori",
    answer3: "Fugi",
    answer4: "Chiyo",
    correctAnswer: "Chiyo"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who is the first enemy Naruto faces?",
    answer1: "Mizuki",
    answer2: "Orochimaru",
    answer3: "Zabuza",
    answer4: "Kabuto",
    correctAnswer: "Mizuki"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "How does Karin heal you?",
    answer1: "You summon her",
    answer2: "She bites you",
    answer3: "She ethces your name on her skin",
    answer4: "You punch her",
    correctAnswer: "She bites you"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who was the youngest Jonin?",
    answer1: "Kakashi",
    answer2: "Itachi",
    answer3: "Neji",
    answer4: "Naruto",
    correctAnswer: "Kakashi"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What piece of jewelry do the Akatsuki wear?",
    answer1: "Rings",
    answer2: "Nose Rings",
    answer3: "Earrings",
    answer4: "Anklets",
    correctAnswer: "Rings"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "At the beginning of Naruto, what is Sasuke's goal?",
    answer1: "Kill his brother",
    answer2: "Take over the world",
    answer3: "Become hokage",
    answer4: "Impress sakura",
    correctAnswer: "Kill his brother"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which sword did Suigetsu originally wield?",
    answer1: "Samehada",
    answer2: "Nuibari",
    answer3: "Shibuki",
    answer4: "Kubikiribōchō",
    correctAnswer: "Kubikiribōchō"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does ANBU mean?",
    answer1: "Special Unit forces and recruits",
    answer2: "Special Assassination and tactical squad",
    answer3: "Undercover ninjas: black operations",
    answer4: "Hidden Agendas of Shinobi and Allied Tactics",
    correctAnswer: "Special Assassination and tactical squad"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does Gaara's tattoo mean?",
    answer1: "Orphan",
    answer2: "Monster",
    answer3: "Love",
    answer4: "Hate",
    correctAnswer: "Love"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who did Naruto try out his Rasengan on?",
    answer1: "Sasuke",
    answer2: "Jiraya",
    answer3: "Hidan",
    answer4: "Kakuzu",
    correctAnswer: "Kakuzu"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who created the Akatsuki?",
    answer1: "Orochimaru",
    answer2: "Tobi",
    answer3: "Yahiko",
    answer4: "Itachi",
    correctAnswer: "Yahiko"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is Sasuke's team called?",
    answer1: "Tiki",
    answer2: "Taka",
    answer3: "Toka",
    answer4: "Toku",
    correctAnswer: "Taka"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who performs the technique Evening Elephant?",
    answer1: "Ino",
    answer2: "Neji",
    answer3: "Guy",
    answer4: "kakashi",
    correctAnswer: "Guy"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which of these characters has Kurama's chakra?",
    answer1: "Menma",
    answer2: "Sora",
    answer3: "Haku",
    answer4: "Guren",
    correctAnswer: "Sora"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "There's an episode called \"Laughing ____\"?",
    answer1: "Shino",
    answer2: "Orochimaru",
    answer3: "Kakshi",
    answer4: "Shikamaru",
    correctAnswer: "Shino"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What was the name of Madara's jutsu?",
    answer1: "End of suffering",
    answer2: "Eye of the moon",
    answer3: "Endless red moon",
    answer4: "Reflection in red",
    correctAnswer: "Eye of the moon"
  ),

  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Who is the last shinobi that Naruto battled in Naruto Shippuden?",
    answer1: "Madara",
    answer2: "Sasuke",
    answer3: "Kurama",
    answer4: "Kaguya",
    correctAnswer: "Sasuke"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "How old was naruto when he met his father?",
    answer1: "fifteen",
    answer2: "sixteen",
    answer3: "seventeen",
    answer4: "eighteen",
    correctAnswer: "sixteen"
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "How old was kakashi when he joined the anbu?",
    answer1: "eleven",
    answer2: "twelve",
    answer3: "thirteen",
    answer4: "fourteen",
    correctAnswer: "thirteen"
  ),
];

// 45 questions